let questions = [
    {
      numb: 21,
      question: "Which one of the following is not a keyword?",
      answer: "use strict",
      options: [
        "with",
        "if",
        "debugger",
        "use strict"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 22,
      question: "Which one of the following is not considered as “statement” in the JavaScript?",
      answer: "use strict",
      options: [
        "with",
        "if",
        "debugger",
        "use strict"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 23,
      question: "In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
      answer: "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
      options: [
        "block that contains a single statement",
        "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
        "Conditional block",
        "both conditional block and a single statement"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 24,
      question: "In a case, where the value of the operator is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is",
      answer: "object",
      options: [
        "string",
        "undefined",
        "boolean",
        "object"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 25,
      question: "Which one of the following is an ternary operator?",
      answer: "?",
      options: [
        "+",
        "?",
        ":",
        "–"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 26,
      question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression?",
      answer: "immediate if",
      options: [
        "Switch statement",
        "Alternative to if-else",
        "If-then-else statement",
        "immediate if"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 27,
      question: "Which one of the following operator returns false if both values are equal?",
      answer: "==",
      options: [
        "==",
        "!==",
        "!",
        "&&"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 28,
      question: "“An expression that can legally appear on the left side of an assignment expression.” is a well known explanation for variables, properties of objects, and elements of arrays. They are called",
      answer: "Lvalue",
      options: [
        "Prototypes",
        "Properties",
        "Definition",
        "Lvalue"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 29,
      question: "What we will get if we compare the “one” with “8” using the less than operator (“one”<8)?",
      answer: "False",
      options: [
        "NaN",
        "True",
        "False",
        "Undefined"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 30,
      question: "Which type of JavaScript language is",
      answer: "High-level",
      options: [
        "Object-Based",
        "Object-Oriented",
        "Assembly-language",
        "High-level"
      ]
    }
  ];
  